Guide to the New York State Association of Family and Consumer Sciences records, 1908-2009.
New York State Association of Family and Consumer Sciences records, 1908-2009.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
New York State Association of Family and Consumer Sciences records, 1908-2009.
3410
New York State Association of Family and Consumer Sciences.
9.1 cubic ft.
Correspondence, publications, organizational records, financial documents, memoranda, ephemera.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Reports, minutes, resolutions, constitution, bylaws, financial records, correspondence, membership lists, and history of the association; auditors' reports; records of Student Member Section, including budget data, planning guides, national records, handbooks, public relations material, student conventions, and YOUR TIME IS NOW, story of the American Home Economics Association-Student Member Section; membership reports; Board of Directors records; newsletters, programs, memos, annual reports, and records of Southern Tier Chapter; files of the State President of the New York State Home Economics Association, including material on Board activity; records of the Southeast District, N.Y.S.H.E.A.; and correspondence with college chapters. Also, folders from the New York State Future Homemakers of America, 1943-1990. The Association was formally the New York State Home Economics Association.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Reports, minutes, resolutions, constitution, bylaws, financial records, correspondence, membership lists, and history of the association; auditors' reports; records of Student Member Section, including budget data, planning guides, national records, handbooks, public relations material, student conventions, and YOUR TIME IS NOW, story of the American Home Economics Association-Student Member Section; membership reports; Board of Directors records; newsletters, programs, memos, annual reports, and records of Southern Tier Chapter; files of the State President of the New York State Home Economics Association, including material on Board activity; records of the Southeast District, N.Y.S.H.E.A.; and correspondence with college chapters. Also, folders from the New York State Future Homemakers of America, 1943-1990. The Association was formally the New York State Home Economics Association.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State Association of Family and Consumer Sciences.; American Home Economics Association.Student Member Section.; New York State Future Homemakers of America.; New York State Home Economics Association.Southern Tier Chapter.; New York State Home Economics Association.
Subjects:
Home economics.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. History, 1920-1999
Box 1
Series II. Administrative Records
Boxes 1 and 10
Series III. Meeting and Conference Records, 1927-2009
Boxes 2-5, 10
Series IV. Students, 1935-1983
Box 5
Series V. Southern District, 1952-2002
Box 5
Series VI. Western District, 1912-2003
Boxes 6 and 10
Series VII. Southeastern District, 1954-1972
Box 7
Series VIII. Newsletters, 1935-2009
Boxes 7 and 10
Series IX. Ephemera, 1945-1990
Boxes 8, 10, 11
Series X. Clippings and Photographs, 1941-2002
Boxes 9-10
Series XI. Greater New York State, 1908-1915
Box 11
Series XII. Long Island District (LID), 1960-2009
Boxes 10 and 11
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. History, 1920-1999
  - History of home economics/family and consumer sciences, no.1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - History of home economics/family and consumer sciences, no.2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - History of home economics/family and consumer sciences, no.3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Association Past Presidents, 1920-2005 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Letterhead through the years (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Lake Placid Conference Memorial information, 1964, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Information regarding Syracuse china (dishware), 1953 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Definition of home economics, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Founding minutes-Higher education section (colleges and universities), 1965-1969 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Book: National goals and guidelines for research in home economics (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Equal Rights amendment, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Home economics in homemaking programs, 1968-1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Proclamation-150th anniversary of Ellen Swallow Richards, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 65th anniversary Lake Placid Conference, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Lake Placid Conference, information and correspondence (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Name Change, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Creation of Executive Secretary Position, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - NYSHEA Incorporation, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Southeastern District Dissolution, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Eastern District Dissolution, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Central District Dissolution, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Series 2. Administrative Records (Boxes 1 and 10)
  - Member Survey and Reorganization Task Force, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Letters of Agreement-Unified Group (NYSHEA, NYSHEIA, NYSAFCS, NYSAFCSE, NYSAEHE, NYSAEFCS), 1990-2000 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Unified Group Records, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Unified Group Records, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Unified Group Records, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Unified Group Records, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Unified Group Records, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Unified Group Records, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Unified Group Records, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Unified Group Records, 2005-2009 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Handbooks, 1925-1967 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Handbooks, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Handbooks, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Handbooks, 1985-1999 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Constitutions and Bylaws, 1924-1998 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - NYSAFCS: Motions, Executive and Board Meetings, 1984-1999 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Association Financial Annual Reports (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Association Tax Exempt Documents (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Tax Exempt Status, 1955-present (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Income Tax Statements and Correspondence, 1962-1972 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Audited Financial Reports, 1948-1978 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - NYSAFCS Motions, 2000-2009 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Financial Annual Reports, 1993-2009 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - NYSAFCS Audit papers, 2005-2006 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - State Officers, 1920-1962 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Officer Lists, 1993-2010 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Directories, 1996, 1999, 2000, 2003, 2005, 2007, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Budget, 1997-2006 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Annual Report, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Plan of Work, 2007-2011 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Guidelines for Leaders, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - NYSAFCS Awards, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Tax Exempt Forms, 1987-2004 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Series 3. Meeting and Conference Records, 1927-2009 (Boxes 2-5)
  - Executive, Board and Association Records, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee and Board, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Executive, Board and Association Records, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Executive, Board and Association Records, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Executive, Board and Association Records, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Executive, Board and Association Records, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Association Minutes and Reports, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board and Association Records, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Executive, Board and Association Records, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Minutes and Reports, Executive Committee, 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Executive, Board and Association Records, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Executive and Board Minutes and Reports, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Executive and Board Reports, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Executive Committee Minutes and Officer Reports, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Executive Committee Reports, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Executive Committee Reports, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Executive Committee and Board Minutes and Reports, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Association Minutes and Reports, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Association Minutes and Reports, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Association Minutes and Reports, Executive Committee, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Association Minutes and Reports, Executive Committee, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Executive Minutes, Association Reports, 1960-1962 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Executive Committee, Association Reports, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Executive Committee, Association Reports, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Executive Committee, Association Reports, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Executive Committee, Association Minutes and Reports, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Executive Minutes, Board and Association Records, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Executive Minutes, Board and Association Records, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Executive Minutes and Reports, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Executive Minutes, Association Minutes and Reports, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Executive Minutes and Reports, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Executive Minutes, Association Minutes and Reports, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Executive Minutes, Association Minutes and Reports, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee Minutes and Reports, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee Minutes and Reports, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Executive Minutes and Reports, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Executive Minutes and Reports, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Executive Committee and Association Records, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Executive Committee and Association Records, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Executive Minutes, Association Minutes and Reports, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Executive Minutes, Association Minutes and Reports, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Executive, Board and Association Records, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Executive Minutes, Association Minutes and Reports, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee, Association Minutes and Reports, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Executive Minutes and Reports, Board Records, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Executive Minutes, Association Minutes and Reports, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Executive Minutes, Association Minutes and Reports, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Executive Minutes, Association Minutes and Reports, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Executive Minutes, Association Minutes and Reports, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee, Association Minutes and Reports, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Executive Minutes, Association Minutes and Reports, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Executive Minutes, Association Minutes and Reports, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Association Minutes and Reports, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Executive Minutes, Association Minutes and Reports, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Executive Minutes, Association Minutes and Reports, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Executive Minutes, Association Minutes and Reports, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Executive Minutes, Association Minutes and Reports, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Executive Minutes, Association Minutes and Reports, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Executive Minutes, Association Minutes and Reports, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Association Minutes and Reports, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Association Minutes and Reports, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Association Minutes and Reports, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Association Minutes and Reports, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Association Minutes and Reports, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Association Minutes and Reports, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Association Minutes and Reports, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Association Minutes and Reports, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Association Minutes and Reports, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Association Minutes and Reports, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Association Minutes and Reports, 2000-02 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 2000-2009 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 2000-2009 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Member Meeting Minutes, 2000-2006 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Conference Program: Centennial "Celebrating the Past, Sustaining the Future", 2009 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Series 4. Students, 1935-1983 (Box 5)
  - Career/Guidance Information, 1943-1949 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Curriculum Materials (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Student Member Section: Minutes and Reports (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Student Member Section: Minutes and Reports and Newsletter, 1935-1979 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Student Member Handbook, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Student Member Section, 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Series 5. Southern District, 1952-2002 (Box 5)
  - NYSHEA Southern District Minutes, 1952-1958 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - NYSHEA Southern District Minutes, 1959-1964 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - NYSHEA Southern District Minutes, 1965-1969 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - NYSHEA Southern District Minutes, 1970-1975 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - NYSHEA Southern District Meeting Minutes, 1976-1981 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - NYSHEA Southern District Meeting Minutes, 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - NYSHEA Southern District Meeting Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - NYSHEA Southern District Meeting Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - NYSHEA Southern District Meeting Minutes, 1990-1995 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - NYSHEA Southern District Meeting Minutes, 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - NYSHEA Southern District Meeting Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - NYSHEA Southern District Meeting Minutes, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Southern District Handbooks and Bylaws, 1972-1999 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Southern District Newsletters, 1972-2000 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - NYSHEA Southern District Officers List (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - NYSHEA Southern District Membership Lists (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - NYSHEA Southern District Membership Lists (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - NYSHEA Southern District Newsletter, 1956-1978 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Video: "Celebrating Our Past, Building Our Future", 2002 (Box 5)
- Series 6. Western District, 1912-2003 (Box 6)
  - Western District NYSHEA President's Reports, 1951-1953 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - NYSHEA Constitution (Western District Included) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - American Association of Family and Consumer Sciences-Western District, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Certification (Home Economist) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1934-12-1939-04 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - American Association of Family and Consumer Sciences-Western District (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - NYSHEA-Western District, 1989/1991 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1949-1954 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1953-05-1954-09 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, 1982-1985 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Niagara Frontier Group, Home Economics in Business Newsletter, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - NYSHEA Western District Minutes, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - NYSHEA Western District Newsletter Buss Session, 1951-1954 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - NYSHEA Western District Annual Reports, 1949-1954 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - NYSHEA Western District Bank Statements and Receipts, 1979-08-1980-07 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - NYSHEA Western District Bank Statements and Receipts, 1980-07-1981-07 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - NYSHEA Western District Bank Statements and Receipts, 1981-07-1982-07 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Career Day, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - NYSHEA Western District Minutes, 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - NYSHEA Western District Minutes, 1944-1945 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - NYSHEA Western District Minutes, 1946-1948 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - NYSHEA Western District Minutes, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - NYSHEA Western District Minutes, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - NYSHEA Western District Minutes, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - NYSHEA Western District Minutes, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - NYSHEA Western District Minutes, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - NYSHEA Western District Minutes, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Radio Programs, 1945-1955 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Publicity Reports, 1943-1952 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Fundraising Flyers (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - NYSHEA Western District Minutes, 1924-1933 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - NYSHEA Western District Minutes, 1934-1939 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - NYSHEA Western District Minutes, 1940-1941 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Ledger, 1924-1930 (Box 6)
  - Ledger, 1930-1962 (Box 6)
  - Ledger, 1962-1976 (Box 6)
  - Members and Officers, 1951-1955 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Members and Officers, 1946-1950 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Members and Officers, 1941-1945 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Members and Officers, 1912-1940 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Handbooks of Officers' Duties (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Clippings, 1939-09-1943-05 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - News Clippings (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Miscellaneous Activities, 1984-1988 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Booklet, pt. 1 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Booklet, pt. 2 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Booklet, pt. 3 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Records of the district, May 2003-2006 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Central Western District Reports, 1996-2009 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Western District Reports, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Series 7. Southeastern District, 1954-1972 (Box 7)
  - NYSHEA Southern District (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Minutes and Records, 1954-1956 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Minutes and Records (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Minutes and Records, Directory, 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Minutes and Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Minutes and Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Minutes and Records, 1961-1963 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Minutes and Records, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Minutes and Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Minutes and Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Minutes and Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Minutes and Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Minutes and Records, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Minutes and Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Minutes and Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Minutes and Reports (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Southeastern District Newsletter, 1981-10 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Series 8. Newsletters, 1935-2009 (Boxes 7 and 10)
  - Newsletters, 1935-1949 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Newsletters, 1950-1966 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Newsletters, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Newsletters, 1970-1976 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Newsletters, 1977-03-1983-10 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Newsletters, 1984-10-1987-02 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Newsletters, 1988-03-1991-02 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Newsletters, 1992-2002-03 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Newsletters, 2000-02-2009-10 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Series 9. Ephemera, 1945-1990 (Boxes 8 and 10)
  - Ephemera-Future Homemakers of America (FHA), 1945-1950 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Prospectus for FHA, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - State Meeting Programs, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters, 1964-1989 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Ephemera-FHA, 1950-1959 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Ephemera- FHA, 1960-1969 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Ephemera-FHA, 1970-1979 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Ephemera-FHA, 1980-1986 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Ephemera-FHA, 1987-1989 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - National Materials, 1957-1973 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - National Leadership Meetings Programs, 1968-1975 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - National Leadership Meetings Programs, 1976-1988 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Teen Times, 1968-1979 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Teen Times, 1980-1988 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Action Education: Using Study Circles to Build Student Leadership Teams, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees, 1985-1989 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Historical Documents for FHA, n. 1 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Historical Documents for FHA, n. 2 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - FHA-brochures, newsletters (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - FHA-Home Economics Related Occupations (FHA/HERO), 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - NYSHEA-Awards (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - NYSHEA-newsletters, archival records and information (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Roll-New York State Future Homemakers of America, Absolute Charter, 1969-06-27 (Box 8)
  - Box containing pins, ring, emblems, 1950, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Video-"Study Circles: Democracy in Action" (Box 8)
  - Video-"Facilitating Action Education" (Box 8)
  - Letterhead (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - NYSHEA Scarf (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Series 10. Clippings and Photographs, 1941-2002 (Boxes 9-10)
  - Scrapbook of Clippings, 1941-10-1944-03 (Box 9)
  - Scrapbook of Clippings, 1945-01-1947-01 (Box 9)
  - Scrapbook of Clippings, 1952-04-1953-04 (Box 9)
  - Scrapbook of Clippings, 1975-10-1980-04 (Box 9)
  - Home Economics Photographs and Clippings, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Historical Photographs, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Workshop: "Home Economists: Pacesetters for Working with Low-Income Families", 1969 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Association Photographs and Clippings, 1970-1987 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Scarf and Tag Photographs (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, 1980-2002 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Series 11. Greater New York State, 1908-1915 (Box 10)
  - Records of the Home Economics Association of Greater New York (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Book of recorded minutes
- Series 12. Long Island District (LID), 1960-2009 (Boxes 10 and 11)
  - Long Island District(LID) Newsletters, 1961-1980 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - LID Newsletters, 1981-1992 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - LID Newsletters, 1993-2001 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - LID Bylaws and Handbooks, 1960-1992 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - LID Minutes of Meetings, 1961-1964 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - LID Minutes of Meetings, 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - LID Minutes of Meetings, 1968-1970 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - LID Minutes of Meetings, 1971-1973 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - LID Minutes of Meetings, 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - LID Minutes of Meetings, 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - LID Minutes of Meetings, 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - LID Minutes of Meetings, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - LID Minutes of Meetings, 1986-1988 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - LID Minutes of Meetings, 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - LID Minutes of Meetings, 1992-1994 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - LID Minutes of Meetings, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - LID Minutes of Meetings, 1998-2000 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - LID Minutes of Meetings, 2001-2003 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - LID Minutes of Meetings, 1961-1969 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - LID Minutes of Meetings, 1970-1998 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1963-2000 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Ellen Swallow Richard Tributes, 1992-12-03 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Convention-LID Report, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - LID Reports, 2002-2009 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - NYSHEA Conventions and events-programs and brochures, 1964-1983 (Box 11, Folder 24)